giveawayservice.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Giveaway Service

This Privacy Policy describes GiveawayService.com's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. GiveawayService.com receives your information through our website. When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by GiveawayService.com in the United States or any other country where GiveawayService.com operates.

### Information Collection and Use

We value your privacy as much as we do our own, so we’re committed to keeping your personal and business information safe. We’re uncomfortable with the information companies, governments, and other organisations keep on file, so we ask for only the bare minimum from our customers. We’ll never use your personal information for any reason other than why you gave it, and we’ll never give anyone access to it unless we’re forced to by law.

Any information collected via a third party API is public information authorized by you before we can access it. Once access is given all information is accessed via third party secured API’s as long as you authorize access via a secured token or key. The information that is displayed on GiveawayService.com is used by its users to understand if a brand or influencer is a good fit for their campaign. All data accessed by GiveawayService.com is GDPR compliant in accordance withe EU Data Protection rules. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

Information Collected Upon Registration: When you create or reconfigure a GiveawayService.com account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, username, password, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your name and username, is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results. Some Services, such as search, public user profiles and viewing lists, do not require registration.

Additional Information: You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as product information, description, and a picture. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or the instructions on our web site. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional.

Log Data: Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms.

Cookies: Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as searching and looking at public profiles or promotions. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. GiveawayService.com may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

Third Party Services: GiveawayService.com uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services, such as hosting our various blogs and wikis, and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Tip We do not disclose your private information except in the limited circumstances described here.

Your Consent: We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your GiveawayService.com account.

Service Providers: We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy.

Law and Harm: We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect GiveawayService.com's rights or property.

Business Transfers: In the event that GiveawayService.com is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

Non-Private or Non-Personal Information: We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public promotions or the number of users who clicked on a particular link (even if only one did).

### Third Party Services

GiveawayService.com uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services, such as hosting our various blogs and wikis, and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request.

Facebook: When connecting to facebook using fconnect we will ask for certain information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“personal information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your full name, gender, birthday, address, and amount of facebook friends. We keep your entire information private except the total number of friends which is displayed to promoters who you have voluntarily applied for their promotion.

Google: When connecting to Google using Google Analytics we will ask for certain information about you that can be used to contact or identify you and your blog (“personal information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your url, number of visits, visitors, unique visitors, average time on your website, and time zone. We keep your entire information private to the public and only show the personal information listed above to promoters that you voluntarily apply for their promotion.

Twitter: When connecting to twitter using your twitter username we will ask for certain information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“personal information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to the total number of twitter followers. We keep your entire information private to the public and only show the personal information listed above to promoters that you voluntarily apply for their promotion.

Alexa: When connecting to Alexa using your blog url we will ask for certain information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“personal information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your blogs Alexa ranking. We keep your entire information private to the public and only show the personal information listed above to promoters that you voluntarily apply for their promotion.

Instagram: When connecting to Instagram using your Instagram account we will ask for certain information about you that can be used to contact or identify you ("personal information"). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, total number of Instagram followers. We keep your entire information private to the public and only show the personal information listed above to promoters that you voluntarily apply for their promotion.

YouTube: When connecting to Youtube using your Youtube account we will ask for certain information about you that can be used to contact or identify you ("personal information"). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, total number of Youtube followers. We keep your entire information private to the public and only show the personal information listed above to promoters that you voluntarily apply for their promotion.

### Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

### Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

### How to complain

We take complaints very seriously. If you’ve any reason to complain about the ways we handle your privacy, please contact us by email at support@giveawayservice.com.

### Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at /privacy-policy. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

_This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 24th, 2018._
